Lesson 5. Ted goes out for the evening.
Ted leaves to go visit his girlfriend, Amber.
Ted's mother, Susan, says she doesn't really like Amber.
She wishes him a good time anyway.
See you later, mom.
Where are you going, Ted?
I told Amber I'd drop by.
What are you two going to do?
Maybe go to the movies or to a party.
Our plans are still up in the air.
Why don't you invite her over here?
I don't want to hang around here.
Dad is really down in the dumps.
Is Amber the girl with the nose ring and the purple hair?
Yeah, I'm crazy about her.
Don't take this the wrong way, but she's not exactly my cup of tea.
Take it easy, mom.
We're not about to get married.
We just enjoy hanging out together.
I guess there's no accounting for taste.
Have a good time.
Don't worry. We'll have a blast.
That's what I'm afraid of.